A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Art, Series C FA340
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Canceled Art Files, 1949-1979; 6; 10 Cubic Feet
  - Photo Files (Gorky - Grilley) (Box 14, Folder 77)
    Gorky, Arshile; Gottlieb, Adolph; Grammatopoulos, Constantine; Grapner, Ernest; Grausman, Philip; Graves, Morries; Gray, Cleve; Grebank, Dorothy; Greenbaum, Dorothea; Greenly, Colin; Grief, Harriet; Grieshaber, H.A.P; Grigorian, Marcos; Grilley, Robert
  - Photo Files (Grilo - Guastella) (Box 14, Folder 78)
    Grilo, Sarah; Gris, Juan; Gross, Anthony; Gross, Chaim; Grosshardt, Edwin F.; Guarducci, Otello; Guastella
  - Photo Files (Guayasamin - Gwathmey) (Box 14, Folder 79)
    Guayasamin; Guerin, A.M.; Guglielmi, Louis; Guinzburg, Ruth L.; Gunther, Max; Guston, Philip; GUt, Jean Jacques; Guttuso, Renato; Gwathmey, Robert
  - Photo Files (Haacke - Hartley) (Box 14, Folder 80)
    Haacke, Hans; Haas, Richard; Haas, Terry; Hadengue, Sebastien; Haese, Gunther; Hagiwara, Hideo; Hamblett, Theora; Hannaula, Simo; Hanspers, Olle; Harnett, William; Hart, George Overbury; Hartigan, Grace; Hartley, Marsden
  - Photo Files (Haas - Hartley) (Box 14, Folder 80a)
  - Photo Files (Hartung - Hyde) (Box 15, Folder 81)
    Hartung, Hans; Hayes, David V.; Hayter, Stanley William; Heise, William Zack; Helion, Jean; Hepworth, Barbara; Herrara; Hillier; Himme, Alice; Hirsch, Stefan; Hnizdovsky, Jacques; Hoag, Peter; Hoff, Margo; Holden, Norman; Hollaway, Antony L.; Homer; Hosiasson, Philippe; Hugo, Breton Edouard; Huig, Henk; Hultberg, John; Hunziker; Hurtado, Angel; Hyde, Scott
  - Photo Files (I) (Box 15, Folder 82)
    Ichikawa, Sadao; Ihle, John; Ihlenfeld, Klaus; Inagaki, Tomoo; Indiana, Robert; Iqbal, Geoffrey; Isobe, Yukihisa; Item, Georges; Ivanjicki, Olja
  - Photo Files (J) (Box 15, Folder 83)
    Jaeckel, Willi; Jawlensky, Alexej; Jeio; Jelinek, Hans; Johns, Jasper; Johnston, Ynez; jones, E. Powis; Joseph, Jasmin; Jules, Marvin
  - Photo Files (Kalaitzidou - Kitoaka) (Box 15, Folder 84)
    Kalaitizidou, Charoula; Kalinowski, Horst Egon; Kandinsky, Wassily; Karoly, Frederic; Kearls; Kelly, Ellsworth; Kent, Norman; Kerg, Theo; Kierzkowski, Bronislaw; Kikuhata, Mokuma; Kimball, Edward J.; Kimura, Shigeru; King, William D.; Kirchner, Ernst Ludwig; Kitaoka, Fumio
  - Photo Files (Klee) (Box 15, Folder 85)
    Klee, Paul
  - Photo Files (Klieman - Koenig) (Box 15, Folder 86)
    Kliemann, Carl-Heinz; Kline, Alma; Kline, Franz; Knipschild, Robert; Kobashi,Yasuhide; Kobezdej, Aleksander; Koenig, Fritz
  - Photo Files (Kohn - Kuegler) (Box 15, Folder 87)
    Kohn, Gabriel (Gabe); Kolar, Jiri; Kolbe, Georg; deKooning, Willem; Kornburst, Leo; Koud; Krasinski, Edward; Krause, Glen; Kreisel, Harold; Kruck, Christian; Kruger, Louise; van Kruiningen; Kuegler, Rudolph
  - Photo Files (Lacey - Laurent) (Box 16, Folder 88)
    Lacey, Ninon; Lachaise, Gaston; Lacroix, Richard; La Fresnaye, Roger de; Lam, Wilfredo; Lamonica, Roberto de; Langlais, Bernard; Lapinski, Tadeus; Larkin, Eugene; Larson, Ardena; Laurencin, Marie; Laurens, Henri; Laurent, Robert
  - Photo Files (Lawrence - Lichtenstein) (Box 16, Folder 89)
    Lawrence, Jacob; Lebenstein, Jan; Lehmbruck, Wilhelm; Liberman, Alexander; Liberman, Sandu; Licari, Enrico; Lichtenstein, Roy
  - Photo Files (Liebermann - Lytle) (Box 16, Folder 90)
    Liebermann, Max; Lindner, Richard; Lipichitz, Jacques; Lipton, Seymour; Lippold, Richard; Litto, Frank; Lockwood, George; Lorne, Naomi; Louis, Morris; Lowe, Maxine; Lurcat, Jean; Lytle, Richard
  - Photo Files (Leger) (Box 16, Folder 91)
    Legar, Fernand
  - Photo Files (Leger) (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - Photo Files (Mabiel - Magana) (Box 16, Folder 93)
    Mabiel; Mac Donald, John; Machlin, Sheldon; Mac Iver, Loren; Mack, Heinz; Magalhaes, Aliosio; Magana, Mardonio
  - Photo Files (Magnelli - Marca-Reilli) (Box 16, Folder 94)
    Magnelli, Alberto; Magritte, Rene; Maillol, Aristide; Maiorana, Ronald; Mallary, Robert; Malone, Robert; Manolo; Manz, Curt
  - Photo Files (Marcks - Mathieu) (Box 17, Folder 95)
    Marcks, Gerhard; Margo, Boris; Martins, Maria; Marin, Hugo; Marini, Marino; Marquet, Albert; Martinez, Richard; Marx, Robert E.; Martinelli, Ezio; Maselli, Modesta; Masson, Andre; Masurovsky, Gregory; Matare, Ewald; Mathieu, George
  - Photo Files (Matisse) (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Photo Files (Matisse) (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Photo Files (Matsumoto - Miro) (Box 17, Folder 98)
    Matsumoto, Akira; Meeker, Dean J.; Meredith, John; Micossi, Mario; Millares, Manolo; Miller, Richard: Millman, Edward; Mills, Roland; Minguzzi, Lucieno; Minne, Georges; Mirko, Basaledella; Miro, Jean
  - Photo Files (Modigliani - Monroe) (Box 17, Folder 99)
    Modigliani, Amedeo; Mondrain, Piet; Monroe, Keith
  - Photo Files (Montenegro - Morg'io) (Box 17, Folder 100)
    Montenegro, Roberto; Moore, Henry; Mopope, Steven; Moran, Edward Percy; Morandi, Giorgio; Morgan, Norma; Morg'io
  - Photo Files (Morris - Music) (Box 17, Folder 101)
    Morris, Robert; Mosca, Ivan; Moussia, Alves; Moy, Seong; Muccini, Marcello; Munakata, Shiko; Munch, Edvard; Mundt, Ernest; Munter, Gabriele; Murphy, Catherine; Music, Zoran Antonio
  - Photo Files (N) (Box 17, Folder 102)
    Naudelman, Elie; Nakaian, Reuban; Nevelson, Louise; Nicholson, Ben; Noguchi, Isamu; Nura
  - Photo Files (O) (Box 18, Folder 103)
    O...; Ober, Hermann; Obin, Philome; Obregon, Alejandro; Ocamp, Miguel; Oda, Shigeru; O'hara, Frederick; Okada, Kenzo; Ozenfant, Amedee
  - Photo Files (Pagliacci - Phillips) (Box 18, Folder 104)
    Pagliacci, Aldo; Parker, Andrew Robert; Patterson, Guy; Pedroza, Raoul; Pennell, Joseph; Pepper, Beverly; Perez, Rodolfo P. Peterdi, Gabor; Peto, John Frederick; Phillips, Bert Greer
  - Photo Files (Picasso) (Box 18, Folder 105)
    96 Etchings; 3 Nude Women; Album; Balzac, Honore de; Bearded Man; Bull, Horse, and a Woman on the Ground; Coiffure; Compoistion Blue au POssin; Composition H; Corrida; Danae; Dancers
  - Photo Files (Picasso) (Box 18, Folder 106)
    Deux Buveurs Catalans; Deux Clowns; Eight Nudes; Etude de Femme; Etude de Profils; Femme au Fichu; Femme au Singe; Figure; Garcon a Cheval; Girl with a Mandolin; Guitar and Fruit Bowl; Guitar on Table; Head; Head in Browns and Black
  - Photo Files (Picasso) (Box 18, Folder 107)
    Homme a l'Agneau et Personnages; Interior with a Girl Drawing; Job; La Bouteille de Bass; La Femme et Le Magot; La Femme Peintre et Le Modele; La Guitare; La Pique Cassee; La Tauromaquia; Le Cirque
  - Photo Files (Picasso) (Box 18, Folder 108)
    Leda; Le Depart; Le Frere Mendiant; Les Modeles; Les Moissonneurs; Le Torero, Ceret; Maisons Sur La Colline; Mere, Danseur et Musicien; Minotauromachy
  - Photo Files (Picasso) (Box 18, Folder 109)
    Modeles Posant; Mother and Child; Nessus and Dejanire; Nude de Dos; Owl; Pitcher and Bowl of Fruit; Portrait of Dora Maar; Reclining Woman; Red and White Owl; Reverly, Pierre; Sheet of Studies of Nudes and Bulls; Student with a Pipe; Study for Actor; Study for GUitar on Table; Study for Violin; Study for a Hand
  - Photo Files (Picasso) (Box 19, Folder 110)
    Sylvette Sur Pond Rouge; Tapestry After Acrobat; Tapestry Oedipus and Sphnix; Tete de Taureau; Toror en Vallauris; The Nest; Two Seated Men; Verres et Fruits; Vie Marc; Visite a L'atelier; Woman's Head; Woman in a Striped Boddice; Woman with Mandolin
  - Photo Files (Pierce - Pugh) (Box 19, Folder 111)
    Pierce, Danny; Pierce, Leona; Pignon, Edouard; Pollock, Jackson; Ping-Ming, Hsiung; Pistoletto, Michelangelo; Piza, Arthur Luiz; Plate, Walter; Poleskie, Steve; Poliakoff, Serge; Portinari, Candido; Pugh, T.
  - Photo Files (Rafael - Rosenthal) (Box 19, Folder 112)
    Rafael, B.; Raible, Alton; Rainz, E.; Ramos Blanco. Teodoro; Rauschenberg, Robert; Raussmuller, Urs; Raveau, Marcel; Redar, Bernard; Redon, Olin; Reiner, Imre; Reinhold, Nono; Renoir, Auguste; Renzi, Clement; Reynal, Jeanne; Richards, William F.; Richier, Germaine; Richterich, Marco; Rickey, George; Riopelle, Jean-Paul; Rivera, Diego; Rivera, Manuel; Roberts, William K.; Robinson, Gladys Lloyd; Rodin, Auguste; Rodriguez-Lorrain, Emilio; Rogers, Gertrude; Romano, Clare; Romijn, Gust; Ronald; Rosenquist, James; Rosenthal, Bernard
  - Photo Files (Rostand - Runacher) (Box 19, Folder 113)
    Rostand, Michel; Rothko, Mark; Rouault, Georges; Rozendaal, J.W.; Ruiz Matute, Miguel; Runacher, Suzanne
  - Photo Files (Sacilotto - Schwartz) (Box 19, Folder 114)
    Sacilotto, Deli; Saetti, Bruno; Saff, Donald; Saito, Kiyoshi; Salazar, A.; Salisbury, Frank O.; Salles, Francis; Sam, Bal Krishna; Sanchez, Emilio; Sanchez, Enrique; Sanders, Ludwig; Sani, Alberto; Santomaso, Giuseppe; Savelli, Angelo; Schanker, Louis; Scheibe, Fred Karl; Schenck; Schelip, Angelo; Schina, Mary; Schmidt, Julius; Schmidt, Katherine; Schoffer, Nicolas; Schrag, Karl; Schulz, Hans Wolfgang; Schwartz, Aubrey
  - Photo Files (Schwitters - Skaggs) (Box 19, Folder 115)
    Schwitters, Kurt; Scipone (Gino Bonichi); Seley, Jason; Seguin-Bertault, Paul; Sekine, Yoshio; Sekino, Jun'ichiro; Seliger, Charles; Seligmann, Kurt; Seymour; Shahn, Ben and Leonard Baskin; Shahn, Ben Shahn, Ben and Stefan Martin; Sharp, Joseph Henry; Shaub, Paul; Sheeler, Charles; Sherman, Arline; Shivitz, Barbara; Shokler, Harry; Sickert Sills, Joyce; Simbari, Nicholas; Siquerios, David Alfano; Sivers, Kent M.; Skagg, Robert Lee
  - Photo Files (Smith - Steig) (Box 20, Folder 116)
    Smith, David; Sok, Ap; Solbert, Ronnil Sonenberg, Jack; Soto, Jesus; Soulages, Pierre; Sowers, Robert; Spencer, Niles; Spruance, Benton; Srbinovic, Mladen; Stahly, Francois; Stamos, Theodoroes; Stankiewicz, Richard; Steffanoni, Attilio; Steig, William
  - Photo Files (Steinberg - Szyszlo) (Box 20, Folder 117)
    Steinberg, Saul; Stella, Frank; Stremel, Max Arthur; Stolen, Oddbjorn; Sugai, Kumi; Summers, Carol; Sung, Lee Hang; Sutherland, Graham Vivian; Suzuki, James; Sykes, Maltby; Szyszlo, Fernando
  - Photo Files (Taeuber-Arp - Torres-Garcia) (Box 20, Folder 118)
    Taeuber-Arp, Sophie H.; Takahashi, Shinichi; Takahasi, Rikiol Takal, Peter; Takeda, Sadayuki; Takies, Vassilakis; Tamayo, Rufino; Tanaka, Ryohei; Tanguey, Yves; Tarbox, Christine; Tate, Nairne; Tchelitchew, Pavel; Teruz, Orlando; Thorton, Leslie T.; Tinguely, Jean; Titone, Simone; Tobey, Mark; Togetsukyo; Tomaszewski, Lubomir; Tomlin, Bradley; Toneyama, Kojn; Tooker, George; Torralba, Juan Jose Toorop, Jan Theadoor; Torres-Garcia, Joaquin
  - Photo Files (Toulouse-Lautrec - Truninger) (Box 20, Folder 119)
    Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri de; Trozzi; Truninger, Max
  - Photo Files (Uchima - Walters) (Box 20, Folder 120)
    Uchima, Ansei; Uecker, Gunther; Ueno, Nagao; Valenti, Italo; Vallotton, Felix Edouard; Valtat, Louis; Van Dongen, Kees; Van Gogh, Vincent; Van Hoessen, Beth; Vasarely, Victor; Vespignani, Renzo; Vickery, Robert; Viesulas, Romas; Villacis, Anibal; Villalta, Mariano; Viteri, Oswaldo; Vlaminck, Maurice de; Volk, Leonard Wells; Vollmer, Ruth; Vuillard, Jean Edouard; W...; Wagenaar, Kossje; Walters, Carl
  - Photo Files (Wan Shan - Wou-ki) (Box 20, Folder 121)
    Wan-Shan, Yau; Warhol, Andy; Watanbe, Sadao; Weber, Max; Wehrlin, Robert; Weinberg, Francis B.; Weiss, Emil Rudolf; Weiss, Harvey; Weissauer; Wells, Charles; White, H. Donald; Wilde, John; Wilkie, Ulfert S.; Williams, Walter; Wilson, ALbert; Winner, W.R.; Winter, Fritz; Wojciechowsky, Agatha; Wood-Thomas, Alan; Wortman, Denys; Wou-ki, Zao
  - Photo Files (Yamguchi - Z) (Box 20, Folder 122)
    Yamaguchi, Katsuhiro; Yordan, Yehuda; Yoshida, Hodaka; Yoshida, Masaji; Yoshihara, Hideo; Youkeles, Anne; Youngermann, Jack; Yrizarry, Marcos; Yunkers, Adja; Zadkine, Ossip; Zajac, Jack; Zeidmann, Robert; Zemer, Yigal; Ziegler, Laura; Ziemann, Richard Claude; Zorach, William; Zorn, Andres Leonard; Zuloaga, Iganeio; Zweepardt
  - Photo Files (Sections 1-5) (Box 21, Folder 123)
  - Photo Files (Sections 6) (Box 21, Folder 124)
  - Photo Files (Sections 10-11) (Box 21, Folder 125)
  - Photo Files (Sections 12-50) (Box 21, Folder 126)
  - Photo Files (Mary Clark Rockefeller) (Box 21, Folder 127)
  - Index Cards (Box 22)
    Restricted - Confidential Material.